Mandil Malla

Tama-Ku, shukugawara6-6-21lindesidekui103, Kawasaki

07085570709

mallamandilcoding@gmail.com

100

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mandil-malla/

www.mandilmalla.me

As a highly motivated computer engineering graduate with a strong passion for technology, I possess over 6 months of experience in development using PHP, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS for a company based in Nepal back in 2017. Additionally, I have gained valuable management skills through my experience in the restaurant service field in Japan, where I also achieved JLPT N3 certification. Recently, I successfully completed Le Wagon's Web Development Bootcamp and have been dedicated to continuously enhancing my skills and staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends.

Experience

JAN 2023 - MAR 2023

Projects/Le Wagon (Web Development Bootcamp), Tokyo Portfolio

- Different projects done throughout the available time
- Portfolio

Tokyo Run Buddy

- Mobile web application that provides suggestions to users based on their preferences
- Backend Ruby on Rails Frontend html, css, js , bootstrap
- Website (login credentials: sutairusu@me.com, 123123)

Camera Equip

- Camera Rental web application
- Backend Ruby on Rails Frontend html, css, js, bootstrap
- Website (login credentials: mallamandilcoding@gmail.com, 123123)

Travel Website

- Responsive website using frontend html ,css ,js
- Website

JUN 2019 - JAN 2023

Sub Manager/Antworks Co. Ltd (Restaurant), Tokyo

- Managing stocks and shifts
- Guiding newcomers
- Handling kitchen/hall

DEC 2016 - JUN 2017

Programmer/ ABGS Group, Nepal

- Worked on making chat-bots project
- Used php, html, css, js, mysql, git

Skills

- Html5
- Css3
- Ruby / Ruby on Rails
- BootStrap
- Javascript
- SQL

Education

APRIL 2016

Bachelor in Computer Engineering/Advanced College of Engineering & Management, Nepal

PHP

Certifications

JAN 2023 - MAR 2023

Web Development/Le Wagon, Tokyo

FEB 2017 – MAY 2017

Front End Development/Halftone Design, Nepal

Languages

- Nepali (native)
- English (Business)
- Japanese (N3)
- Hindi (conversational)

Activities

• Basketball • Movies • Cooking